{
    "questions":[
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is responsible for sprint meeting?",
            "answers":[
                "Scrum team",
                "Scrum master",
                "Product Owner",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "1",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "When acceptance testing is performed in Agile development?",
            "answers":[
                "On request of customer",
                "After system is ready",
                "At the end of each iteration",
                "Daily"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "2",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Select One Type of nonfunctional requirement?",
            "answers":[
                "user requirements",
                "product requirements",
                "Efficiency requirements",
                "2+3 is the two Correct Answers"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "2",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
	  {
            "question": "Which one of the following is not a step of requirement engineering?",
            "answers":[
                "elicitation",
                "design",
                "analysis",
                "documentation"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "1",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
	  {
            "question": "Types OF Reviews:",
            "answers":[
                "Formal Reviews",
                "Peer Reviews",
                "The answers 1 & 2 are correct",
                "There are no correct answers"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "3",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
		{
            "question": "In Peer Review,the primary function is to use the skill of a group of people to",
            "answers":[
                "identify needed improvements",
                "certify correctness",
                "encourage uniformity & enforce subjective rules",
                "all of the above"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "3",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
        	{
            "question": "The UML was designed for describing:",
            "answers": [
                "object-oriented systems",
                "architectural design",
                "SRS",
                "Both object-oriented systems and Architectural design"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "2",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
		{
            "question": "What's true about MVC?",
            "answers": [
                "a Software Architecture’s Element",
                "a software Application Architecture",
                "a software Architecture patterns",
                "There is no correct answer"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "1",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
		{
            "question": "Software Maintenance includes",
            "answers": [
                "Error corrections",
                "Enhancements of capabilities",
                "Deletion of obsolete capabilities",
                "All of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "3",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
		{
            "question": "What type of software testing is generally used in Software Maintenance?",
            "answers": [
                "Regression Testing",
                "System Testing",
                "Black-box testing",
                "White-box testing"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "1",
            "level": "3",
            "team": "giraffe"
		},
           {
            "question": "what is unit testing?",
            "answers": [
                "is running the code",
                "is testing a method by software developers",
                "is to debuging all the code",
                "is to testing all parts of a project"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "2",
            "level": "2",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the advantages of writing unit tests?",
            "answers": [
                "Code maintainability as good unit tests enforces",
                "Code testability",
                "Design testability",
                "all the above"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "2",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "Software can be tested as :",
            "answers": [
                "Black Box",
                "White Box",
                "answers one and two are correct",
                "none of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "1",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
	  {
            "question": "Agile software engineering refers,",
            "answers": [
                "A philosophy and a set of development guidelines",
                "An active and continuous communication between developers and customers",
                "Encourages customer satisfaction",
                "All of the mentioned above"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "4",
            "level": "3",
            "team": "giraffe"
        },
        {
            "question": "________ specification is also known as SRS document",
            "answers": [
                "white-box",
                "grey-box",
                "black-box",
                "none of the mentioned"
            ],
            "correct_ans": "3",
            "level": "1",
            "team": "giraffe"
        }
    ]
}
